Heh, this is fun. L've never used
a hydraulic thermoforming press before.
It's pretty sweet, huh?
(Howard:)This little baby set the university back
a hundred and seventy-five grand.
(Leonard:)That's three minutes.
(Leonard:)- Should we see what we got?
- Hang on.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah.
This is one good-looking panini.
- Hand me the tuna meIt.
- Yup.
(Howard:)Thank you.
(Howard:)How's it going
with the long-distance love affair?
It's not easy,
but we're making it work.
(Howard:)When you say making it work...
(Howard:)...does that include
doing the cyber-nasty?
- What?
- You know, the virtual pickle tickle, heh.
The digital:
(Raj:)Dude, this is my sister
you're talking about.
(Howard:)Hey, Leonard jiggling his junk at her
through a webcam...